Finally we're going to talk about any none and no very very common.
最后，我们将讨论任何无和非常非常常见的。
And the best way to really learn these is by example to get a feeling for them.
真正学习这些的最好方法是通过例子来感受它们。
Any can be used for questions and it can also be used as an answer to the same question.
Any 可用于问题，也可用作同一问题的答案。
The most common question is do you have any.
最常见的问题是你有没有。
Plus the thing you could just say Do you have any.
加上你可以说的东西你有吗。
I need some chocolate.
我需要一些巧克力。
Do you have any.
你有什么。
I don't have any.
我没有。
We don't say I have any.
我们没有说我有。
We would say I have some.
我们会说我有一些。
So we would use any if it's an answer.
所以如果它是一个答案，我们会使用任何。
Only if it's when it's zero.
只有当它为零时。
The amount is zero.
金额为零。
We have none.
我们没有。
We don't say I have any.
我们没有说我有。
We never say that but when we ask the question we can say Do you have any.
我们从不这么说，但当我们问这个问题时，我们可以说你有吗。
Do you have any.
你有什么。
Do you have any chocolate.
你有巧克力吗？
I don't have any.
我没有。
This is how it's used.
这就是它的使用方式。
None is usually at the end of the sentence.
None 通常在句末。
She gave me none.
她没有给我。
I got none.
我没有。
There was none.
没有。
Usually it goes at the end of the sentence and it means it means zero means zero.
通常它出现在句子的末尾，这意味着它意味着零意味着零。
No then is usually followed by something else unless it's a statement to answer a question a yes no
否 then 通常后面跟着其他东西，除非它是回答问题的陈述 a 是 否
question.
问题。
Do you want to go.
你想去吗。
No.
不。
But if we're talking about an amount of something this classes about quantifies the amount to zero then
但是，如果我们谈论的是本课程所涉及的将数量量化为零的东西，那么
we would say no.
我们会说不。
Plus the thing for example we have no time.
加上例如我们没有时间的事情。
We have no time.
我们没有时间。
We have very little time means we have some but almost no time.
我们只有很少的时间意味着我们有一些但几乎没有时间。
If it's zero we can say no time.
如果它是零，我们可以说没有时间。
We have no time.
我们没有时间。
We need to go.
我们得走了。
So let's look at some examples and you can get a better feeling for this.
因此，让我们看一些示例，您可以对此有更好的感觉。
I don't want any help.
我不想要任何帮助。
Do you need any help.
你需要帮助吗。
Remember it can be used in a question.
请记住，它可以在问题中使用。
We wouldn't say I want any help.
我们不会说我需要任何帮助。
We would say I really I really need some help.
我们会说我真的我真的需要一些帮助。
I really need your help but if it's no.
我真的需要你的帮助，但如果不是。
If it's 0 I don't.
如果是0，我不会。
I don't want any help.
我不想要任何帮助。
I don't need any help.
我不需要任何帮助。
Did you find any quarters quarters are twenty five cents.
你有没有发现任何四分之一的硬币都是二十五美分。
Twenty five cents that we use in America.
我们在美国使用的 25 美分。
Did you find any quarters.
有没有找到宿舍。
No.
不。
None or I could say I didn't find any quarters.
没有，或者我可以说我没有找到任何宿舍。
I didn't find any.
我没有找到。
So as a question did you find any as an answer.
所以作为一个问题，你有没有找到任何答案。
No none noticed that none goes by itself.
没有人注意到没有一个是自己去的。
And if I want to say I didn't find any.
如果我想说我没有找到。
That is also totally OK.
这也完全没问题。
All right.
好的。
I asked for help.
我寻求帮助。
I got none notice that none is at the end of the sentence.
我没有注意到句末没有任何内容。
There's nothing after it.
之后就什么都没有了。
We don't usually put anything after none.
我们通常不会在没有之后放置任何东西。
We already stated the thing we're talking about.
我们已经说明了我们正在谈论的事情。
We're talking about help.
我们正在谈论帮助。
OK.
好的。
I asked for help.
我寻求帮助。
We know we're talking about help.
我们知道我们在谈论帮助。
Then the next thing we say is I got none.
然后我们说的下一件事是我没有。
I got no help.
我没有任何帮助。
I could say I got no help.
我可以说我没有得到任何帮助。
Or could we use any.
或者我们可以使用任何一个。
Yes we could.
是的，我们可以。
We could say I didn't get any help.
我们可以说我没有得到任何帮助。
So all of those are OK.
所以所有这些都可以。
They're the same thing.
他们是一样的。
I got none.
我没有。
I got no help.
我没有任何帮助。
I didn't get any help.
我没有得到任何帮助。
Same thing.
一样。
I basically got no help.
我基本上没有任何帮助。
Basically got no help.
基本上没有任何帮助。
I have no time left.
我没有时间了。
I have little time left.
我剩下的时间不多了。
I have no time left now.
我现在没有时间了。
Can that be used to understate something.
可以用来低估某事吗。
Sometimes if we're in a big hurry we might have a few minutes but we don't want to say we have a few
有时如果我们很着急，我们可能有几分钟，但我们不想说我们有几个
minutes a little time.
分钟一点时间。
So we say I'm sorry I have no time.
所以我们说对不起，我没有时间。
I have no time.
我没时间。
OK we're emphasizing that we don't want to give any of our time.
好的，我们强调我们不想付出任何时间。
Don't want to give any of our time.
不想给我们任何时间。
There are no more books.
没有更多的书了。
So this is often used.
所以经常使用这个。
No more is used.
不再使用。
Followed by the thing that we're talking about.
接下来是我们正在谈论的事情。
I got no help.
我没有任何帮助。
We say help after No.
我们在 No 之后说帮助。
No more books books goes after no no time.
没有更多的书没有时间。
Time goes after No.
时间流逝在No之后。
Did you get any help.
你有没有得到任何帮助。
None.
没有任何。
Are there any books.
有没有什么书。
No.
不。
None.
没有任何。
Nothing after that.
之后就什么都没有了。
So these examples I hope make any none and no very very clear.
因此，我希望这些示例可以使任何一个都没有，也没有非常非常清楚。
And make sure you practice these and look out for them as your reading or as you're speaking with others.
并确保您练习这些并注意它们作为您的阅读或与他人交谈时。
Pay attention to when they're used because the more examples you see the better of an understanding
注意何时使用它们，因为您看到的示例越多理解越好
you can get for these phrases and quanta fires although they're very simple are extremely important
你可以得到这些短语和量子火焰虽然它们非常简单但非常重要
and you need to feel super duper comfortable with them in order to use them naturally when you speak.
你需要对它们感到超级舒服，以便在你说话时自然地使用它们。
OK so if you didn't already you should have a very clear picture of how different quanta fires are used
好的，所以如果您还没有，您应该非常清楚地了解如何使用不同的量子火
to express different quantities different amounts.
表示不同的数量不同的金额。
The best way to really get a natural feeling for them because you can know them but not really know
真正获得对他们自然感觉的最佳方式，因为您可以了解他们但并不真正了解
how to use them when you're speaking the best way to naturally get a feeling for them to really use
当你说话时如何使用它们 自然地感受它们真正使用的最佳方式
them is to practice practice practice until they become habits.
他们就是练练练练，直到成为习惯。
I can't express that enough one part of learning is knowledge.
我无法充分表达学习的一部分就是知识。
One part of learning is habits.
学习的一部分是习惯。
Habits come through practice and repetition practice makes perfect.
习惯是通过练习来的，重复练习是完美的。
So make two sentences for every quanta fire that we learned in this lesson.
因此，为我们在本课中学到的每个量子火造两个句子。
Try to make two clear sentences of different types.
试着写出两个不同类型的清晰句子。
OK then if you want to read through them and record them that would be a good idea.
好的，那么如果您想通读它们并记录它们，那将是一个好主意。
You can listen to your pronunciation and see if you can make any corrections.
你可以听听你的发音，看看你是否可以做出任何更正。
And if you want to make more than two sentences more than two examples that is just fine.
如果你想制作两个以上的句子，多于两个例子，那很好。
The more practice the better.
练习得越多越好。
Hey good luck.
嘿，祝你好运。
I'll see you in the next lesson.
我们下节课见。